budapestaffiliateconference.com 2014-04-14

# Privacy Policy | Budapest Affiliate Conference

###  Information collection and use

We collect information from our users at several different points on the website - this is for customer service and billing purposes, we also collect data from our users so that we can customise the site according to individual selections. iGaming Business Ltd is the sole owner of the personal information collected from this site.

###  Registration

In order to receive our email alerts, users have to complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and e-mail address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as business sector), and unique identifiers, but encouraged so we can provide a more personalised experience.

###  Order forms

We request information from users on our order forms. Users have to provide contact information (such as name and delivery address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiry date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill customer orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user

###  Cookies

A cookie is a small text file written to a user’s hard drive that contains the User ID. The cookies do not contain any personal information about users. The use of cookies is now widespread. The reason we use cookies is to save our users time on the site (so that users do not have to log in with a password more than once); and also so that we can personalise a user's experience of the site. If a user sets up his browser to reject the cookie, he or she may still use the site although functionality will be impaired.

###  Log files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

###  Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that iGaming Business Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of these third party sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

###  Newswires

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newswires, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

###  Surveys

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose any information requested. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and delivery address), and demographic information (such as business sector). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the functionality of the site.

###  Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, as will be the case for most of the time that a user is browsing the web.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact [Customer Services.](mailto:info@igamingbusiness.com?subject=T&C%20Form%20Query)

###  Correcting/Updating personal information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your postcode), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the personal profile page or by contacting [Customer Services](mailto:info@igamingbusiness.com?subject=T&C%20Form%20Query).

###  Notification of changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
